
[
    {
      "question": "좋다",
      "answer": "To be good"
    },
    {
      "question": "싫다",
      "answer": "To be bad"
    },
    {
      "question": "덥다",
      "answer": "To be hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "춥다",
      "answer": "To be cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "슬프다",
      "answer": "To be sad"
    },
    {
      "question": "아프다",
      "answer": "To be sick or in pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "피곤하다",
      "answer": "To be tired"
    },
    {
      "question": "재미있다",
      "answer": "To be interesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "재미없다",
      "answer": "To be boring"
    },
    {
      "question": "어렵다",
      "answer": "To be difficult"
    },
    {
      "question": "쉽다",
      "answer": "To be easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "깨끗하다",
      "answer": "To be clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "더럽다",
      "answer": "To be dirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "빠르다",
      "answer": "To be fast"
    }
  ]
  